<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RoomList>
    <Room id="1"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>The sealed dead end</name>
        <location>1</location>
        <description>This is where it all started, You are at a dead end of hallway. In here you can see a very dim light hanging in front of you far away. A man is suddenly asking from the corner of the dead end behind you: "What is your name, my young friend"?</description>
        <northRoomNumber>0</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>0</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>2</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>0</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="2"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>The corner for tomorrow</name>
        <location>2</location>
        <description>It looks like all the people who came here all walked along the small stepping stones to the right in the floor. But there is a door with a lot of wood covered on it in front, it looks interesting, it has a small lit tourch on it, burning out.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>1</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>0</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>0</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>3</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="3"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>The long hall</name>
        <location>3</location>
        <description>There is only a small dim light far far away ahead of you.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>0</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>2</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>0</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>4</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="4"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>Round table</name>
        <location>4</location>
        <description>You just entered an opening with the light on a big roundtable infront of you. Room enough for 20 kings or queens. The walls is covered in spiderweb and dust. It's kind of creapy in here. Hurry up south or east, there is openings. But to the north there is a door.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>5</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>3</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>11</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>0</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="5"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>A big kitchen with pots of sawed legs and arms</name>
        <location>5</location>
        <description>The is blood everywhere. Pots, pans is standing in the corners of the room, floating with sawed of legs and arms sticking out of them. It all looks like king rings on most of the fingers and toos. To the west and south, there is a small doors you could try.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>0</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>0</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>4</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>6</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="6"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>Four chests placed in a cross, with alter in middle</name>
        <location>6</location>
        <description>This looks like an old abandod king cementary. The alter in the middle has the crows of the four kings standing in direction of each chest. Don't try to pickup item's inside the chests in here, it will bring you bad luck. A small door is to the east, but a door is also to the north and oh also to the west.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>7</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>5</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>0</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>20</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="7"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>A big room with torture tools all over</name>
        <location>7</location>
        <description>A bed with spikes, a breathing horse standing with eyeclaps in front of a streching tool. You have entered the torture buffet. Hope you will never meet the punisher. There is a an opening to the south a door to the west and a door to the north.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>9</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>0</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>6</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>8</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="8"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>A prison with a lot of chains hanging in sealing</name>
        <location>8</location>
        <description>You are entering a door and sees, Oh shit, this is the skeleton prison. There is a skeleton of a person hanging in the sealing, inside a metal box. Chains is all over the sealing. you have no other choice but to go back where you came from.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>0</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>7</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>0</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>0</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="9"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>Big barrols of wine filling up the room in a mace</name>
        <location>9</location>
        <description>Wholy shit ! barrols of wine like towers in the sky. How to get pass this ! It is like a damn mace to go through ! You can try the door to the east or go to the south.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>0</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>10</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>7</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>0</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="10"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>End wall covered in a massive painting with gods and monsters fighting together</name>
        <location>10</location>
        <description>This is a damn, forsanken room, you have just opened the door and it screams women screams, like new years eye roars with fireworks. THEN it all stops. You enters the room and sees that the end wall all covers a huge painting of kings, queens, soldiers, farmers, ghosts, dragons, zombies all fighting other with blood all over the painting, but one Big Chest is standing on top of all the dead bodies. But it is just a painting, so you have to go back.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>0</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>0</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>0</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>9</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="11"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>Puke on the walls</name>
        <location>11</location>
        <description>Both side walls is covered in puke and it stinks like shit all over! You can only continue south or north.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>4</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>0</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>12</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>0</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="12"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>A big tree is growing from the floor</name>
        <location>12</location>
        <description>Wood roots all over in the floor. It looks a tree has been growing through the floor and through the sealing only sticking out some small leaves. you have to continue around the big root foot to the west or north.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>11</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>0</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>0</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>13</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="13"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>Deadbody's covered in autumn leaves all over the floor</name>
        <location>13</location>
        <description>Wow, it suddenly became a long hall, with autumn leaves all over! But why. You take the first step and hits something. SHIT it is a deadbody, and realises there is deadbody's sticking out through the leaves all over the hall. You can only jump on top of them, through the hall to the west or east.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>0</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>12</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>0</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>14</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="14"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>The wall figure of the great bull</name>
        <location>14</location>
        <description>A giant room opens suddenly up. to the south the wall is covered with a big bull carved into the wall with very mean eyes and ring in the noose. You can go to the west, north and east only</description>
        <northRoomNumber>17</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>13</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>0</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>15</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="15"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>Jawbroken faces all over the walls</name>
        <location>15</location>
        <description>What the f*ck, the wall is covered in faces but ! the jaw is gone. Of my god ! who places all these faces here, must have been insane in there minds. You have one choice but to go north or east.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>16</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>14</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>0</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>0</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="16"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>A big crocodille mouth opening out to the real world in the horizon across the canyon far far away.</name>
        <location>16</location>
        <description>Freedom ! at least it looks like it exists in the horizon. But it is to far away, well you can only go back to the disaster place you came from.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>0</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>0</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>15</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>0</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="17"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>Uprising narrow stairway with loose steps</name>
        <location>17</location>
        <description>Damn this is tight and looks high. The stairs rises up towards something, but you can't see. The steps is VERY loose, shit, if i fall it goes far far down a stair. You can only go north or south.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>18</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>0</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>12</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>0</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="18"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>The floor covered as one big grill with lake running below</name>
        <location>18</location>
        <description>The water running as a lake is sounding from beneath your feet. Looking down you are standing on a huge fence grill working like the floor on top the river running below. But the water is to dark to see anything down there. There is openings to the north, west and south.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>20</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>0</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>17</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>19</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="19"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>A deep and dark well with torturing sounds coming from within</name>
        <location>19</location>
        <description>People are roaring, screaming, sounding hurt, crying most of the time, from within a well in front of you, but it is not just a well, it has no water in it and is dark as core of hell it self. Trying to reach down you find the fence with a lock. Shit can't go any further then back where you came from.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>0</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>18</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>0</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>0</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
    <Room id="20"> //OneBased index - Easy input in lists etc.
        <name>Balcony covered in flowers</name>
        <location>20</location>
        <description>This room is covered in flowers all over the walls, floor and sealing. Only a balcony opening in the NorthWest corner, like a light focus in the cover of flowers. But you will never be able to climp there. The flowers is all hanging and very losy, don't try to climp, you will hurt your self. You can go south or east.</description>
        <northRoomNumber>0</northRoomNumber>
        <eastRoomNumber>6</eastRoomNumber>
        <southRoomNumber>18</southRoomNumber>
        <westRoomNumber>0</westRoomNumber>
    </Room>
</RoomList>